Viewers all over the world, I release you in the name of Jesus from the pain of the past!
I release you from deep hurt.
Be released!
I release you in the name of Jesus!
Viewers once again, listen:
I release you, in the name of Jesus from the pain of the past!
Be released in the name of Jesus!
Whether you are right or wrong, you have no right to hold unto an offence.
I release you in the name of Jesus!
Be released in the name of Jesus!
Countless people, I mean countless Christians are imprisoned by offence.
It is a trap; it is an effective instrument used by satan.
I release you in the name of Jesus!
If you are a victim, I release you, in the name of Jesus!
Be released!
Pray along with Prophet T.B Joshua.
Touch the screen by faith in Jesus name.
Lord have your way.
I give your my heart.
We believe that you have been inspired by the clip that you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up to date with the latest prophecies, deliverances, services and testimonies
from the Synagogue Church Of All Nations.
Emmanuel TV - Changing lives, changing nations and changing the world
CR Robert Begier 09/04/2019